Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
Mus. Arc. 3.1
Perry, J. Warren
35 containers (2110 photographs; 58 CD-ROMs)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Chiefly photographs of opera singers and productions, with additional photographs of other musicians, ensembles, and performing venues. Many of the photographs bear inscriptions to Dr. Perry.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dr. J. Warren Perry
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection has been digitized and is available in the UB Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Dr. J. Warren Perry was born in Richmond, Indiana in 1921. He earned his B.A. at DePauw University in 1944, his Master's at Northwestern University in 1952, and his Ph.D. at Northwestern in 1955. Dr. Perry has been on the faculties at the University of Illinois at Chicago, Northwestern Medical School, and the University of Chicago. He was also employed as deputy assistant commissioner for research and training in the Vocational Rehabilitation Administration at the Department of Health, Education and Welfare in Washington, D.C. Dr. Perry is the founder of the School of Health Related Professions (now the School of Public Health and Health Professions) at the University at Buffalo, The State University of New York. He served as dean of the school from its founding in 1967 until 1977.
Dr. Perry has devoted much of his life to supporting the arts. Before moving to Buffalo he was one of the founders of the Lyric Opera Company in Chicago. Since arriving in Buffalo Dr. Perry has served as chairman or board member for several local organizations, including the Buffalo Philharmonic, Community Music School, Theodore Roosevelt Inaugural National Historic Site, Artpark, and Friends of the Center for the Arts. The numerous awards granted to honor Dr. Perry's contributions to the community include the Buffalo Arts Councils' Supporter of the Arts award, the Buffalo Distinguished Citizen Award, and national Outstanding Philanthropist Award.
Scope and Content Note
The J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs consists of approximately 2110 photographs. The focus of the collection is opera, with images of singers, productions, conductors, and opera halls. There are also photographs of ensembles and instrumentalists. Many of the photographs bear inscriptions from the artists to Dr. Perry. The documentation is international in scope and is a striking visual record of many of the most significant musicians of the twentieth century.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into eight series:
I. People. Arranged alphabetically by surname.
II. Productions. Arranged alphabetically by name of composer, opera, and opera company.
III. Ensembles. Arranged alphabetically by name of ensemble.
IV. Concert Halls. Arranged alphabetically by city and then by hall (with exception of Tanglewood, filed under T).
V. Duplicates.
VI. Oversize.
VII. Digitized Images.
VIII. Additional Photographs. Photographs received after receipt of original gift. Chiefly portraits of people, arranged alphabetically.
Container List
- People, circa 1910-1971, I.; 1199 photographs
  Photographs of people, chiefly alone in portrait settings. Many of the opera singers are in costume for their respective operatic roles.
  Arranged alphabetically by person's surname.
  - Kurt Adler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-001)
  - Kurt Adler, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-002)
  - Licia Albanese as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 1, Item C01-003)
  - Licia Albanese as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 1, Item C01-004)
  - Licia Albanese as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Camuzzi, M (Box 1, Item C01-005)
  - Licia Albanese as Cio-Cio San, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-006)
  - Licia Albanese as Marguerite in Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 1, Item C01-007)
  - Licia Albanese as Liu with Eugene Tobin as Calaf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 1, Item C01-008)
  - Frances Alda as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-009)
  - Victor Alessandro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Gillings (Box 1, Item C01-010)
  - Enzio Altobelli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-011)
  - Luigi Alva as Count Almaviva, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 1, Item C01-012)
  - Lorenzo Alvary as Raimondo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-013)
  - Lorenzo Alvary as Tristram, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-014)
  - Lucine Amara as Micaela, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-015)
  - Lucine Amara as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-016)
  - Lucine Amara as Nedda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-017)
  - Lucine Amara as Tatyana, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-018)
  - Geza Anda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Glass, Douglas (Box 1, Item C01-019)
  - Marian Anderson as Ulrica, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-020)
  - Marian Anderson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-021)
  - Marian Anderson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-022)
  - Marian Anderson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-023)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-024)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Cio-Cio-San, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-025)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Marguerite, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-026)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Violetta, 11/19/1959, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-027)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-028)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-029)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Martha, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-030)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Melisande with Martial Singher as Pelleas, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-031)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Manon with Nicolai Gedda as Des Grieux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-032)
  - Victoria De Los Angeles as Martha and Rosalind Elias as Nancy, 1961, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-033)
  - Ernest Ansermet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Jackson, Ray Lee (Box 1, Item C01-034)
  - Ernest Ansermet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-035)
  - Ernest Ansermet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Moss Photo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 1, Item C01-036)
  - Charles Anthony as Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-037)
  - Claudio Arrau, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 1, Item C01-038)
  - Claudio Arrau, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Newman (Box 1, Item C01-039)
  - Franco Autori, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-040)
  - Franco Autori, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-041)
  - Felix Ayo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-042)
  - Salvatore Baccaloni as Bartolo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-043)
  - Salvatore Baccaloni as Fra Melitone, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-044)
  - Salvatore Baccaloni as Dr. Dulcamara, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-045)
  - Gina Bachauer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-046)
  - Wilhelm Backhaus, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Namuth, Hans (Box 1, Item C01-047)
  - Carlo Badioli as Dr. Dulcamara, 1953-1954, 1 black and white photograph; Rota (Box 1, Item C01-048)
  - Carlo Badioli as Don Bartolo, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-049)
  - Carlo Badioli in Boheme, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 1, Item C01-050)
  - Carlo Badioli as Warlaam, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Ghizzoni (Como, Italy) (Box 1, Item C01-051)
  - Paul Badura-Skoda, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 1, Item C01-052)
  - Rose Bampton, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 1, Item C01-053)
  - Rose Bampton, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Shelburne (Box 1, Item C01-054)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Amneris, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-055)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Azucena, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-056)
  - Fedora Barbieri in Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Vera Fotografia (Box 1, Item C01-057)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Adalgisa with Anita Cerquetti as Norma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Locchi (Box 1, Item C01-058)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Amneris, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-059)
  - Fedora Barbieri in Gluck's Orfeo ed Euridice, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 1, Item C01-060)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Mistress Quickly, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 1, Item C01-061)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Amneris, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 1, Item C01-062)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Medea, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 1, Item C01-063)
  - Fedora Barbieri as Dalila, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 1, Item C01-064)
  - Sir John Barbirolli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-065)
  - Daniele Barioni as Rodolfo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-066)
  - Daniele Barioni as Pinkerton, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-067)
  - Howard Barlow, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-068)
  - John Barnett, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rothschild Photo (Box 1, Item C01-069)
  - Bela Bartok, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-070)
  - Bruno Bartoletti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-071)
  - Ettore Bastianini as Lescaut, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-072)
  - Ettore Bastianini as Edgardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item C01-073)
  - Ettore Bastianini as Giorgio Germont, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C01-074)
  - Ettore Bastianini as Figaro?, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 1, Item C01-075)
  - Ettore Bastianini as Count di Luna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item C01-076)
  - Kurt Baum as Don Jose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 1, Item C01-077)
  - Kurt Baum as Manrico, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 1, Item C01-078)
  - Kurt Baum as Radames, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 1, Item C01-079)
  - Sir Thomas Beecham, 1956 Jan.-Feb., 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-001)
  - Eduard Van Beinum, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Cor van Weele (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (Box 2, Item C02-002)
  - Eduard Van Beinum, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; De Groot, Godfried (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (Box 2, Item C02-003)
  - Eduard Van Beinum, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Netherlands Information Service (Box 2, Item C02-004)
  - Mimi Benzell, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 2, Item C02-005)
  - Teresa Berganza as Angelina, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-006)
  - Erna Berger, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-007)
  - Carlo Bergonzi as Don Jose, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 2, Item C02-008)
  - Carlo Bergonzi as Canio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 2, Item C02-009)
  - Leonard Bernstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Whitestone Photo (Box 2, Item C02-010)
  - Leonard Bernstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-011)
  - Walter Berry as Guglielmo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 2, Item C02-012)
  - Walter Berry as Lescaut, 1957 Nov., 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 2, Item C02-013)
  - Walter Berry as Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 2, Item C02-014)
  - Walter Berry as Figaro with Christa Ludwig as Cherubino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 2, Item C02-015)
  - Frances Bible as Octavian, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 2, Item C02-016)
  - E. Power Biggs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bachrach, Fabian, 1917- (Box 2, Item C02-017)
  - E. Power Biggs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-018)
  - Rudolf Bing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 2, Item C02-019)
  - Rudolf Bing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 2, Item C02-020)
  - Invitation to meet Rudoph Bing at Indiana University, 1951, 1951 May 8, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-021)
  - Jussi Bjorling as Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 2, Item C02-022)
  - Jussi Bjorling, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-023)
  - Jussi Bjorling as Edgardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-024)
  - Jussi Bjorling as Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 2, Item C02-025)
  - Jussi Bjorling as Cavaradossi, 1959 Nov. 21, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-026)
  - Jussi Bjorling with family, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-027)
  - Sigurd Bjorling as Boris Godunov, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Rydberg, Enar M (Box 2, Item C02-028)
  - Theodore Bloomfield, 1957 July, 1 black and white photograph; Villoresi (Rome, Italy) (Box 2, Item C02-029)
  - Karl Bohm, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-030)
  - Karl Bohm, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-031)
  - Kammersänger Kurt Böhme as Baron Ochs, 1954 Oct. 12, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 2, Item C02-032)
  - Kammersänger Kurt Böhme, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-033)
  - Jorge Bolet, 1957 March, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-034)
  - Jorge Bolet, 1958 June, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-035)
  - Kim Borg as Count Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 2, Item C02-036)
  - Lucrezia Bori as Norina in Don Pasquale, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-037)
  - Lucrezia Bori as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-038)
  - Inge Borkh as Sieglinde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Reed, John E. (Hollywood, Calif.) (Box 2, Item C02-039)
  - Inge Borkh as Salome, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 2, Item C02-040)
  - Inge Borkh as Lady Macbeth, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 2, Item C02-041)
  - Inge Borkh as Salome, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-042)
  - Alexander Brailowsky, 1952 April, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 2, Item C02-043)
  - Gre Brouwenstijn as Desdemona, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-044)
  - Gre Brouwenstijn as Desdemona, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-045)
  - Gre Brouwenstijn, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 2, Item C02-046)
  - Gre Brouwenstijn as Jenufa with Sylvia Fisher as Kostelnicka, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 2, Item C02-047)
  - Gre Brouwenstijn as Sieglinde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 2, Item C02-048)
  - John Brownlee as Count Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-049)
  - John Brownlee, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 2, Item C02-050)
  - Monique de la Bruchollerie, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 2, Item C02-051)
  - Fritz Busch, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-052)
  - Fritz Busch, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 2, Item C02-053)
  - Franco Calabrese in Il convitato di Pietra, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 2, Item C02-054)
  - Franco Calabrese in Il matrimonio segreto by Cimarosa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 2, Item C02-055)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 2, Item C02-056)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 2, Item C02-057)
  - Maria Callas as Amina, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 2, Item C02-058)
  - Maria Callas as Leonora in Il Trovatore, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Fishman, David H (Box 2, Item C02-059)
  - Maria Callas with Athens State Orchestra, 1957 Aug. 5, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 2, Item C02-060)
  - Maria Callas with Athens State Orchestra, 1957 Aug. 5, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 2, Item C02-061)
  - Maria Callas with Athens State Orchestra, 1957 Aug. 5, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 2, Item C02-062)
  - Maria Callas with Athens State Orchestra, 1957 Aug. 5, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 2, Item C02-063)
  - Giuseppe Campora as Rodolfo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 2, Item C02-064)
  - Giuseppe Campora as Edgardo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 2, Item C02-065)
  - Giuseppe Campora as Cavaradossi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item C02-066)
  - Anna Maria Canali as Meg Page in Falstaff, 1956-1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 3, Item C03-001)
  - Anna Maria Canali as Meg Page in Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 3, Item C03-002)
  - Anna Maria Canali as Meg Page in Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 3, Item C03-003)
  - Anna Maria Canali as Meg Page in Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 3, Item C03-004)
  - Maria Caniglia as Leonora in Il Trovatore, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Camuzzi, M (Box 3, Item C03-005)
  - Maria Caniglia as Stephana in Siberia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Crimella (Milan, Italy) (Box 3, Item C03-006)
  - Maria Caniglia as Amelia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 3, Item C03-007)
  - Guido Cantelli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Siegel, Adrian (Box 3, Item C03-008)
  - Guido Cantelli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-009)
  - Guido Cantelli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-010)
  - Renato Capecchi as Germont, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-011)
  - Gabor Carelli as Don Curzio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-012)
  - Gabor Carelli as Gastone, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-013)
  - Rosanna Carteri as Mimi, 1952-1953, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 3, Item C03-014)
  - Rosanna Carteri as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Villani (Box 3, Item C03-015)
  - Rosanna Carteri as Gilda, 1953-1954, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 3, Item C03-016)
  - Rosanna Carteri as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Stampa (Box 3, Item C03-017)
  - Rosanna Carteri as as Liu, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 3, Item C03-018)
  - Rosanna Carteri as Liu, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Bisazza, E (Box 3, Item C03-019)
  - Rosanna Carteri as Zerlina with Rolando Panerai as Masetto, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 3, Item C03-020)
  - Enrico Caruso, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-021)
  - Eleazar de Carvalho, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-022)
  - Robert Casadesus, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-023)
  - Robert Casadesus, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 3, Item C03-024)
  - Marta Montanez Casals (Istomin), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-025)
  - Pablo Casals in rehearsal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-026)
  - Pablo and Marta Montanez Casals, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-027)
  - Walter Cassel as Scarpia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-028)
  - Walter Cassel as Kurvenal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-029)
  - Walter Cassel as Kurvenal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 3, Item C03-030)
  - Laura Castellano as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 3, Item C03-031)
  - George Cehanovsky as Fiorello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-032)
  - George Cehanovsky as Sciarrone, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 3, Item C03-033)
  - George Cehanovsky as Marquis d'Obigny, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-034)
  - Anita Cerquetti as Amelia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-035)
  - Anita Cerquetti as Abigail, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 3, Item C03-036)
  - Boris Christoff as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-037)
  - Boris Christoff as Boris Godunov, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item C03-038)
  - Boris Christoff as Boris Godunov with Rosalind Nadell as Feodora, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 3, Item C03-039)